Huh?
I saw you on there!
You saw me where?
On there!
No, you didn't.
Look, I saw you.
Show me.
Come on, show me.
It changed.
All right, keep going.
Show me.
I ain't seen me.
What you talking about?
You what?
You put your stuff on there?
Ah.
Show me where I'm at, Moo.
You what?
I saw a tire.
Where?
What are you talking about?
It was black.
Where are you talking about, Moo?
Daddy!
Really?
Oh!
Yo!
What's wrong?
Ow, about to cry.
You was about to cry?
Yeah, I like that.
You were about to cry.
Who did that?
Why are you about to cry?
Me did that, man.
From all the hard work that we put in.
You about to cry, Moo?
What's wrong?
Did you put your face up there yet?
Yeah.
Can you see?
I didn't want to cry.
Okay.
Can you hear it?
I feel ready.
Oh!
That was weird.
I don't know.
No problem.
Yeah, ma'am.
I don't go.
I don't know.
I'm down.
So,
you Jeff.